Can you recognize that woman,Liz?
Liz,你能认出那个女人吗?
I think I can, Kate.
我想我认得出来,Kate.
It must be Karen Marsh,the actress.
那一定是女演员Karen Marsh.
I thought so.
我也这样想.
Who's that beside her?
她旁边的那个人是谁?
That must be Conrad Reeves.
一定是Conrad Reeves.
Conrad Reeves, the actor?
Conrad Reeves,那个男演员吗?
It can't be.
不可能是.
Let me have another look.
让我再看一看.
I think you're right!
我想你是对的.
Isn't he her third husband?
他不是她的第3个丈夫吗?
No. He must be her fourth or fifth.
不,他一定是她的第4个或第5个丈夫.
Doesn't Karen Marsh look old!
Karen Marsh看上去不显老嘛!
She does, doesn't she!
是的,谁说不是呢!
I read she's twenty-nine,
我从报上看到她是29岁,
but she must be at least forty.
但她一定至少有40岁了.
I'm sure she is.
我肯定她是的.
She was a famous actress When I was still at school.
当我还是学生时,她就是个著名的演员了.
That was a long time ago, wasn't it?
那是好久以前的事了.是吗?
Not that long ago!
不,没有那么久.
I'm not more than twenty-nine myself.
我自己现在还没29岁呢.